let questions = [
	{
		question: '2 + 2',
		options: ['2', '5', '4', '3'],
		correctIndex: 2,
	},
	{
		question: '5 + 2',
		options: ['7', '9', '3', '6'],
		correctIndex: 0,
	},
	{
		question: '4 + 2',
		options: ['5', '2', '6', '8'],
		correctIndex: 2,
	},
	{
		question: '6 + 3',
		options: ['8', '4', '7', '9'],
		correctIndex: 3,
	},
	{
		question: '7 + 2',
		options: ['8', '9', '5', '6'],
		correctIndex: 1,
	},
	{
		question: '8 + 1',
		options: ['5', '9', '4', '7'],
		correctIndex: 1,
	},
	{
		question: '5 + 5',
		options: ['8', '5', '7', '10'],
		correctIndex: 3,
	},
	{
		question: '7 + 2',
		options: ['9', '5', '4', '6'],
		correctIndex: 0,
	},
	{
		question: '3 + 2',
		options: ['2', '4', '5', '6'],
		correctIndex: 2,
	},
	{
		question: '4 + 3',
		options: ['6', '7', '8', '9'],
		correctIndex: 1,
	},
];
